<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Braam Beresford</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Braam Beresford</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 17:10:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Design</title>
      <link>/projects/junior-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 12:04:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/junior-design/</guid>
      <description>For our Junior design project we created created a system that is able to harvest power from a 170 Watt solar panel and safely deliver it to various charging circuits. The system does power point tracking in order to achieve proper input current and voltages.
Once the Printed Circuit Board (PCB) takes in the solar power it safely charges:
 Sealed Lead Acid (SLA) battery with proper charging curve An 18650 Lithium Ion cell USB-C Power Delivery compatible phones and batteries  The USB-C Power Delivery (PD) protocol allows the charger to negotiate a charging rate to deliver up to 45 Watts of power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 17:10:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am pursuing an Honors Bachelor of Science in Electrical and Computer Engineering at Oregon State University with Junior standing. I am heavily interested in digital logic design with personal projects implementing MIPS in SystemVerilog. I am also pursuing a minor in Computer Science.
I formely interned as an Intergrated Circuit Test Engineer at Hewlett-Packard (HP) developing on silicon analog and digital signal tests. Under a mentor I augmented an existing Teradyne test plan to reduce test times by 40 percent.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>